Guide to the Timothy Dwight College, Yale University, Student Records RU.207
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Timothy Dwight College, Yale University, student records
1960-2009
RU 207
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
123.75
(188 boxes)
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Timothy Dwight College, Yale University.
Timothy Dwight College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-G-1 (YRG 13-G-1), Records of the dean of Timothy Dwight College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Timothy Dwight College, Yale University.
College students; Timothy Dwight College (Yale University); Yale University -- Students
- Impounded Student records for the Classes of 1975-1978, 1969-1978; Accession 1975-A-021
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2064
- Student records for the Classes of 1964-1979, 1960-1979; Accession 1987-A-040
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
  Scope and Contents
  The records are arranged by class, thereunder alphabetically by last name.
  - 1968, 543489
  - 1969, 543482
  - 1970, 543473
  - 1971, 543464
    - Non-graduates
  - 1972, 543456
  - 1973, 543449
  - 1974, 543441
    - Non-graduates
  - 1975, 543435
  - 1976, 543428
    - Non-graduates
  - 1977, 543422
  - 1978, 543415
    - Non-graduates
  - 1979, 543409
  - Non-graduate
- Withdrawn student records, 1980, 1989-2003; Accession 2013-A-038
  Restricted until January 1, 2078
- Letters of recommendation for the Class of 2001, Accession 2013-A-045
  Restricted until January 1, 2076.
- Student recommendations for the Classes of 1997 and 2000, 1997-2000; Accession 2013-A-054
  - Class of 1997
  - Class of 2000
- Student records for the Class of 2007, 2004-2007; Accession 2013-A-059
  Restricted until January 1, 2082.
- Student records for the Class of 2006, 2003-2006; Accession 2013-A-067
  Restricted until January 1, 2081.
  - Withdrawn, 1304946
- Student records for the Class of 2008, 2005-2008; Accession 2013-A-072
  Restricted until January 1, 2083.
  - Withdrawn, 1319249
- Student records for the Class of 2005, 2002-2005; Accession 2013-A-076
  - Withdrawn, 1330169
- Student records for the Class of 2009, 2005-2009; Accession 2014-A-017
  Restricted until January 1, 2084.
  - Withdrawn, 1341277